Finding Aid for the Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- W
  - Williams, Mary Ellen, 9 May 1962 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Mrs. Marian. Undated (Box 4)
  - Williams, Quentin, 11 July 1945 (Box 4)
  - Williamsly, L. A, 16 August 1950 (Box 4)
  - Williamson, Elizabeth C, 19 August 1952 (Box 4)
  - Williamson, P. (7), 13 February 1947 –31 July 1951 (Box 4)
  - Willibrand, W. A. (2), 10 May 1941 –17 January 1942 (Box 4)
  - Williford, Mrs. Mamie, 25 August 1946 (Box 4)
  - Willson, A. Leslie. (6), 12 December 1966 –13 November 1972, undated (Box 4)
  - von Wilpert, ?, 15 October 1952 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Doug, 5 January 1948 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 26 July 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Joy, 23 December 1952 (Box 4)
  - Wilson, William, 28 June 1972 (Box 4)
  - Wiltshire, Susan. Undated (Box 4)
  - Winemiller, Grant W, 16 April 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wing, Donald. (2), 12 October 1943 –9 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Wing, Margaret, 19 December 1936 (Box 4)
  - Winkler, J. S, 25 May 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wislocky, C. M, 9 May 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wissmann, Eva, 17 May 1963 (Box 4)
  - Witkop, Philipp. (4), 29 December 1930 –24 October 1938 (Box 4)
  - Witte, Herman, 26 April 1950 (Box 4)
  - Wittrock, G. L. (44), 17 May 1945 –4 February 1953 (Box 4)
  - von Witzleben, Henry. (11), 19 April 1958 –18 July 1968 (Box 4)
  - Wölcken, Fritz. (2), 1 November 1950, undated (Box 4)
  - Wolf, Fred, 19 October 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wolf, Paul, 8 May 1 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wolf-Robe, ? Undated (Box 4)
  - Wolff, Hans M. (7), 30 November 1951 –26 February 1953 (Box 4)
  - Wolff, Helen, 10 June 1948 (Box 4)
  - Wolff, Kurt. (16), 2 July 1948 –15 February 1955, undated (Box 4)
  - Wolfgang, Erin. (3), 9 December 1962 –11 December 1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Wolfgramm, K. (11), 7 September 1972 –25 September 1973 (Box 4)
  - Wolfradt, William. (2), 6 June 1949 –1 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Wolfson, Alfred, 15 January 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wolfskehl, Marie-Luise. (16), 25 April 1934 –7 January 1935 (Box 4)
  - Wonderley, A. Wayne. (47), 7 February 1967 –19 July 1974 (Box 4)
  - Wood, Ann, 9 April 1953 (Box 4)
  - Wood, Peter M, 14 August 1973 (Box 4)
  - Wood, Ralph C. (5), 15 September 1952 –1 November 1952, undated (Box 4)
  - Wood, ?, 1945 (Box 4)
  - Wooley, E. O. (2), 6 July 1943 –28 September 1943 (Box 4)
  - Woodward, Carol H, 9 July 1946 (Box 4)
  - Workman, John. (6), 29 July 1952 –11 December 1961 (Box 4)
  - Works, George A, 19 July 1945 (Box 4)
  - Wormley, Stanton L. (2), 21 November 1949 –5 January 1950 (Box 4)
  - Wrage, Klaus. (6), 30 August 1931 –10 April 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wright, Mr. and Mrs. Jesse, 1938 (Box 4)
  - Wright, Louis B, 22 April 1952 (Box 4)
  - Wright, Richardson. (2), 29 March 1946 –15 April 1946 (Box 4)
  - Wroblowski, Gisela. Undated (Box 4)
  - Wylie, Craig, 3 May 1948 (Box 4)
- Z
  - Zaüleck, Heidi. (6), 14 June 1935 –25 May 1950 (Box 4)
  - Zibart, Jim, 1 March 1971 (Box 4)